DOUGLAS KIEL

2203 Broadway St. Indianapolis, IN 46205 317-993-1534 seekeroflight75@yahoo.com

Bright, articulate and engaging professional experienced in administration and organization dealing very easily with most technology devices. Gifted in process improvement and adaptability holistic thinking and creativity. Quick to learn anything when given clear explanations.

KEY COMPETENCIES

- > Process Improvement
- > Organization and Detail
- Relationship Building
- ➤ Gifted in Languages

- > Curriculum development
- > Adaptivity
- > Holistic Creative Thinking
- > Responsibility

CODING SKILLS

- > JavaScript
- > HTML
- > CSS
- > Bootstrap
- ➤ jQuery
- ➤ Ajax

- > JSON
- ➤ Node
- Postgres
- Mongo/Mongoose
- > Angular
- > React/Redux

Please feel free to checkout my portfolio at: https://douglaskiel.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amazon Fulfillment Center; Indianapolis

Picker

The warehouse division of Amazon.com

- Picked 110% average of their required quota each day
- Obeyed all safety rules
- Came to work on time everyday

Pristine Clean; Indianapolis and Beech Grove

09/2015 - 12/2016

10/2016 - 01/2017

Janitor

Professional janitorial service to offices all over Indianapolis and the Beech Grove Community School system

- Responsible for 40% of owners personal duties at offices to keep him free for more managerial duties.
- Trusted to take care of any task that is needed for filling in at other employee absences 100% of the time
- Performed highest quality cleaning without complaint in duties and highest praise from employers

Doug Kiel Page Two

McAlister's Deli; Greenwood, IN

06/2012 - 12/2015

Professional serving retail public in every aspect of delivery of service and behind the scenes in operations management

- Responsible for inventory order, maintenance and distribution of merchandise for entire store meeting food budget 100% of time.
- Improved process for inventory and stockroom, cooler and freezer, saving McAllister's 10% of retail costs.
- Excels in customer service to become known one of the most valued employees at the store.

Maewon High School; Suwon, South Korea

03/2011 - 03/2012

English Teacher

Prepared and delivered all curriculum development for all conversational classes for junior year students.

- Responsible for communication, language skills
- Measured behavioral growth
- Tested for speaking abilities with 22% noted average improvement

Center Grove Community Schools; Greenwood, IN

10/2010 - 2/2011

Freelance Teacher

Worked at any school needing a substitute teacher.

- Specialized in Middle and High School
- Taught Science, Spanish, and Special Education

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Ball State University. Muncie, Indiana, B.A. Religious Studies Eleven Fifty Coding Academy Indianapolis, Indiana, JavaScript

CELTA Certification, Bangkok Thailand

Latin proficiency in Translation, Conversation Korean and French
Eta Sigma Phi Classical Languages National Honor Society
Introduction to Computer Programming

Professional and Community Development

Redeemer Presbyterian Church
Harrison Center for the Arts